Parallel world stories usually begin like this
...or so it is
The merciful goddess bestows strength upon the hero.
The Beginning Town
And beloved by the inhabitants of the parallel world
The hero enjoys his adventure in the company of the beautiful heroines.
I thought so.
But these are my heroines.
These are my adventures.
To make matters worse, I suffer from such things.
...and what I've learned since arriving in a parallel world is
I'm unlucky when it comes to parallel universes.
My name is Misumi Makoto, and my life is a farce.
My life was ordinary.
I have breakfast with my family in the morning.
After work, I practice shooting.
I will have dinner afterwards.
After showering, I browse the internet and read books.
Knights of the Parallel World (Part Two)
Oh~ My dad's new book is out!
Misumi
It was a quiet day, like any other.
So it's strange that I'm not sleeping in our house.
Where am I?
First night
Hero... Failure
...you seem calm
Who's there?
Would you believe me if I said I am a god?
No, impossible.
You are about to go to a parallel world.
Therefore, please sign your consent.
Your sudden talk about such a topic is causing me trouble.
That's strange. I heard you were aware of the matter.
Please excuse me.
My name is Tsukuyomi. The Dominator of the Night World.
I came to make you a hero and deliver you to the goddess of the parallel world.
Tsukuyomi? Do you mean as in Tsukuyomi-no-mikoto?
One of the three noble children in Japanese mythology?
Ah, you're very knowledgeable.
What are you doing here, Tsukuyomi-sama?
You don't really know anything.
First, your parents are from a parallel universe.
What?
!What?
Now that I've mentioned it, I haven't met any of our relatives at all.
But a parallel world?
For special reasons
Your parents signed a contract with the goddess of the parallel world
and went to Japan.
They agreed to give her the most precious thing they owned someday.
Does this mean that one of my sisters, Yukiko-Nissan or
Mari, will be taken if I don't go?
.actually
...I understand, I'll go. But
Don't worry, Makoto-dono
I will take it upon myself to dispose of the
numerous products she owns that depict men's dreams!
You are God, a true God!
The contract looks good like this.
Is this the only message you want to send to your family?
.Okay
...permission
What is this?
You will now give up the world you have been living in.
I will give you all the strength I can give you.
Thank you very much... Wait?
O goddess! Do you intend to take him without greeting me?
Oh, Makoto-dono, the goddess you're about to meet
. She has a lot of problems.
But I want you to be as patient as possible.
Good!
Since this is your wish, I will even accept a goddess
... I have never heard of before.
The light is bright!
What? Did you arrive?
...Old Tsukuyomi's strength must have weakened
A- The goddess?
In fact, demons and spirits in this
world began to do as they pleased.
My humans are in a big predicament.
That's why I thought of calling you to help them.
Are you really their son?
You are extremely ugly!
To clarify: This is a reference to the story of the ugly duckling that became a swan.
The probability of becoming a swan is zero.
From which ugly duckling's nest did you come?
However, there will be a period of inactivity for the summons.
Why don't you hurry up and disappear from my sight?
Your very presence is disgusting and annoying.
But you're the one who summoned me!
Oh my! Even your voice is ugly!
I have already found other heroes for my world
So stay at the end of my world and don't defile it with your filth.
What?
I don't like the idea of ​​giving you any power.
But I will give you the ability to understand, speak, read
, and write languages ​​other than human language.
What a headache!
Enjoy your lowly life with the orcs and goblins
But beware of spreading your ugly offspring among my people!
Now get out!
I wonder if the fall will kill him.
I can't stand the thought of him coming back again!
You must be joking!
Are you treating me like a cockroach?
Damn you!
!Makoto-dono
Tsukuyomi-sama!
It never occurred to me that the goddess could go this far.
Well, you'll be fine even if you fall from this height.
What?
The world you lived in was harsh and desolate
, and far removed from our protection.
Your magical and physical strength were under a heavy burden.
You are supposed to be strong in this world by freeing yourself
from that burden.
What a fitting interpretation!
But you will die when your time comes. A warning has been given.
What?
...your body, Tsukuyomi-sama
This communication has drained a great deal of my energy.
I will now have to sleep for centuries.
...not possible
The goddess herself has stripped you of your role as a hero.
There is no longer a need for reservations.
...in my name, Tsukuyomi, i.e., Misumi Makoto
I give you freedom in your new world!
I hope we meet again in the cycle of your rebirth.
...Tsukuyomi-sama
!Okay
...Three days have passed since I fell to this ground
And she began walking towards that towering mountain.
I didn't encounter any humans, animals, or even anything edible.
Can I move after 3 days
without eating because I am a superhuman?
Talking to myself is pointless and achieves nothing.
Three days have passed, then?
Only my own voice, the sound of my footsteps, and the wind are all I hear.
Normally, some kind of event would have happened before
I reached this stage.
I feel lonely.
Someone please help me.
Where is it coming from? Where did this sound come from?
Someone please help me!
From here!
Yes, with pleasure!
Huh?
A dog with two heads?
And a pig wearing clothes?
It doesn't matter! This is better than being alone.
Who are you?
Hello! I'm a human and my name is Makoto.
What?! It's so fast!
I'm delighted to meet you!
Huh?
...disgusting
...I did it
...H- Good
I'm happy to meet you.
What? Why is he talking to a human being?
Why am I talking to a pig?
A- Anyway, everything is fine.
I am a kind and gentle person.
You are not gentle at all.
But I saved you, didn't I?
In other words, I am your ally.
Escape: 1
Okay
impossible
2: Fighting
Okay
Most impossible
3: Surrender
Okay
I understand.
!amazing
In fact, I was lost for three days.
Do you know where I should go to meet other people?
There are no human villages nearby.
This desolate place is known as the wasteland and is located at the ends of the earth.
That vile goddess has already thrown me to the ends of the earth.
A. My name is Emma and I am a Hill Ork.
Ah, my name is Makoto.
Excuse me, but is your village near here?
No, I was on my way to the Holy Mountain.
To offer myself as a sacrifice to Shin-sama
The harbinger of the event appeared!
Several years ago, fog enveloped my village.
Our crops no longer produce yields.
The fog began to dissipate after the offerings were made.
So you have to do this?
There is a place in front of us where you can bathe.
As a token of my gratitude for being saved from the two-headed dog
There you can relieve yourself of the burden of travel.
She is intelligent and her behavior is excellent.
I would save her if I could.
Makoto-sama?
What a fragrant scent, redolent with the aroma of flowers!
...if I had saved this young lady
This suggests that she will become the heroine of my story!
My first meal in days
I've heard that humans are a violent and cruel race.
Perhaps he has subhuman blood running through his veins
; look at his appearance.
I'm sorry for being ugly.
Impossible! The pots are floating!
.إنه مجرد سحر نقل نستعمله بشكل يومي
Can you use magic, Emma-san?
Huh? Can't you use it, Makoto-sama?
No, I absolutely cannot.
Would you be willing to teach me if you don't mind?
Let's start with the basics, then.
I call upon you, O flame that forms the essence of fire.
gunshot
!amazing
This amulet is like a magic key that grants magical energy
properties or changes in its properties.
This spell is difficult to cast
, as it is not in the Orc language.
It seemed to me like the same language
I call upon you, O flame that forms the essence of fire.
gunshot
Wow! I did it!
What should I do now?
Imagine a ball of fire and throw it towards your target.
...I imagine, then? I imagine
And then... my throat!
!Hurrah
Does this mean I have mastered the spell?
I can't believe you did it so easily.
What is your current level, Makoto-sama?
Are there levels?
what is going on?
It measures his level
Let's see
Your level is undoubtedly 200... No, probably 300.
Please hold this paper tightly.
Okay
What level is this?
...good
Level 1
one?
If you wish, shall I teach you other incantations?
Yes, thank you.
Makoto-sama?
To dear Emma-san
Thank you so much for what you did yesterday.
I will take the scroll of spells and equipment you gave me.
This isn't a thank you, but I'll sort this out with
Shin-sama somehow.
.Revelation
I was able to read the scroll of incantations and write a letter.
It must be the power of that vile goddess.
If I disappear after Shin's defeat
, I'll be able to skip the wedding event.
I would like to resolve this matter through dialogue if possible.
But perhaps I should train in case I have to fight.
gunshot
Good, I can do this without saying the incantation.
If I could change the form of
magical energy, I would try this.
That thing serves as a suitable target.
Good. You succeeded.
What?
.Unfortunately
!I'm sorry
Are you cooperating with the Orcs?
They look evil no matter how I look at them.
We were planning to subdue the Orcs using the name Shin.
I rushed things in the end.
It destroyed his lair.
Shin's anger will become a reality.
This is what you deserve.
clouds?
No, is it fog?
According to traditional accounts, Shen Mahar
...a giant capable of creating mirages
But what is normal for me does not apply to this world.
Does he attack by surprise?
It passed peacefully. I'm alive.
The fog is preventing me from seeing.
This fog is also not ordinary.
I avoided it.
Was it my instinct? No
Is this the power that Tsukuyomi-sama gave me?
The gunshot, then?
Receiving a blow with this spell will not bring me
any pain or harm whatsoever.
A wound? Was I wounded? Even though I am immune to fire?
...punch
!directly
...followed
A punch with the back of the hand!
Who is this creature?
I'm supposed to be invincible.
...And now, the conclusion
The rising frog's jump punch!
Shame on you
Shame on you!
What-what is going on?
The matter is settled.
You will drown in the bliss of my memories
, and meet your end.
I'm doing well.
a) Excuse me
Oh~ Hasegawa. What's wrong?
...H- Good
Side braid
She's been styling her hair like this ever since I told her
it suited her.
Doesn't it give her a headache?
Misumi-senpai!
I have always looked forward to you
I love you! Will you go out with me?
What?
To be honest, my appearance isn't great.
I love school, but I'm not exceptionally smart.
...and on top of that
Senpai?
No, no! Wait!
This is very surprising.
Wait!
Don't cry, Hasegawa.
So, we can try this for a while.
And then you can fall in love with me!
!any?
Is this impossible?
No, I can't refuse.
Whoa, then, he's a visitor from another world.
...Huh? This memory
What is this? I've never seen anything like it before.
I want to ask him about this directly and get him to tell me about it.
When I saw you draw your bow, I couldn't take my eyes off you.
That's why I joined the shooting club.
Senpai?
- I understand, thank you Hasegawa.
Please call me by my name!
Call me No-ko-mi
Yes, but we are currently
Let's spend lots of time together
during the summer vacation, Senpai.
A- Yes, I'm looking forward to this.
No, that's not true.
...because then
I cried Hasegawa.
I'm sorry, Hasegawa, for making you play a role
in this comedy sketch.
I began to understand the power that Tsukuyomi-sama had given me.
I can create a hemispherical sphere around
myself and control the space within it.
For example, I can conduct research without being noticed.
I can also strengthen myself
Thank you, Shane, for making me realize how pathetic I am.
What a unique power!
But I no longer harbor any animosity towards him.
Please control your anger.
Although it was merely an illusion reflecting your hidden desire
I am so sorry for making you suffer these feelings.
Was that my deepest desire?
Dear visitor from the parallel world, my name is Shin.
I consider myself an invincible creature because I am a great dragon.
My name is Misumi Makoto.
As you mentioned before, I am a visitor from a parallel universe.
Wouldn't you like to make a contract with me, Makoto-dono?
What?
The knot is a special type of magic that grants several benefits.
When the two parties divide it amongst themselves
The strength of both sides can be increased based on their relative strength.
In other words?
This means I will become your companion, Makoto-dono.
I promise you my hope will not be disappointed.
I am deeply interested in your memories, Makoto-dono.
I look forward to your approval.
How much of my memories did I see?
And what secrets did you discover?
I'm wondering about this. I'm certain the contract will benefit us both.
...you conspirator
Okay! I look forward to our future days.
Like you, I hope our relationship will last for years to come.
Let's perform the ritual of concluding the contract.
We will begin with the 50:50 charter.
Did he surpass me in strength?
Let's try 70:30 then.
It is absolutely unique!
Okay, let's try 80:20!
We are finally getting closer to the right balance.
Although I am effectively his slave
...that doesn't matter, this person
No, I'm looking forward to what my master will do in the future.
It seems to me that the time I will spend with
my master will be the greatest time of my life.
Once again, I look forward to our future together, Mr. Makoto-sama.
A dignified beauty in Japanese clothing?
I prefer you to call me Samurai
You are closer to being a hero than a heroine.
"The Second Night: The Black Doomsday Spider"
Next episode
Black disaster spider